vova.com 2019-12-14

# Vova | Privacy Policy

VOVA uses cookies to provide you with the best experience. If you continue we assume that you consent to receive all cookies on VOVA. Learn more at Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Policy Scope

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Vova collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the Vova website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Vova.

We at Vova know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By using or accessing the services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent to the collection, use, and sharing of your information in the following ways. As a reminder, your use of Vova’s Services is at all times subject to the Terms and Conditions, which includes this Privacy Policy. Any terms not defined in this Policy have definitions outlined in the Terms and Conditions. The privacy policy is governed by the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486).

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, their name, email address, mailing address, and/or credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information. Users have the right to refuse to supply personal identification information, however, it may prevent access to certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about any Users who interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include browser name, type of computer being used, and technical information about Users' means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.

### Web Browser Cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser saves cookies to hard drive for record-keeping purposes and tocreate a site history. Browser settings can be used to prevent cookies be or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If your browser’s cookie function is disabled, some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How We Use Collected Information

Vova collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

(1) Personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

(2) Improve our Site

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from users.

(3) Improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

(4) Process transactions

We may use personal or financial information Users provide when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

(5) Administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site features

We will send Users information they agree to receive regarding topics likely to be of interest to them.

(6) Send periodic emails

The email address Users provide for order processing will be used strictly for sending information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to inquiries, other requests, or questions. If a User decides to opt into our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time a User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or the User may contact us via our Site.

### How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers generic collected demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users for the purposes stated above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given permission.

### Third Party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may change constantly. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Vova has the discretion to update their privacy policy at any time. Any revisions will be updated at the bottom of this page. In order to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect, we encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and note any revisions.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following any revisions added this policy will be deemed as an acceptance of those changes.
